Visit our website for more: turkision.com
No living being was harmed
during the filming of this series.
Episode 113
You love and adore.
You excuse.
You don't know what grief is.
I cried a thousand nights without you.
You didn't deprive
yourself for one night.
You're excused.
Ahmed Ghazali
What a good thing he said, isn't it?
But what made him write these verses
was a great concern he lived.
Love.
Going through a love trouble...
Especially when it is
love from both sides...
No lover should be separated
from the one she loves...
Alçiçek.
Love is the highest
feeling in this world.
Why did you summon me, Mother Sultan?
It is necessary for
lovers to meet, Alçiçek.
We separated you from the one you love.
And we locked you in a cage.
Let's see if you can forgive us.
Come on.
Come on, move your wrists, not your mouth.
It will be fine.
I will make you hold the sword.
So that Bala Hatun will include you among
the The Sisters, Ülgen sis...--
Say, say it.
Speak.
I will take your soul with the sword.
Oh my!
Say one more word and I'll cut
that tongue out of your mouth.
What do you do? We are training.
Isn't there a man in this large
tribe? Why does Osman Bey send you?
Also, why would I train myself?
What does Cerkutay
understand from swords?
Ask me about swords.
You are correct, Gürbüz Alp.
I don't understand what he does.
Osman Bey commanded me.
A Bey's order can not be violated.
Come on.
Take your sword and stand before me.
I told you, take your sword and
stand before me, Ülgen Hatun.
Well.
Attack.
You will look into the
eyes of your enemy...
without being afraid.
You have to protect yourself.
It will make women forget what you know.
Look at me, what am I saying.
You will ask me about the sword.
Why did you come?
Osman Bey is waiting for you
Come on.
Are you saying this now? You...
Practice!
Come on, come on.
- Come on.
- Slow down.
Quickly.
Look at him.
He gets angry too.
Alçiçek.
Loneliness is Allah's only.
People should not be separated
from the one they love.
Let your words match your
actions, Mother Sultan.
What are you saying? You tried to
marry me to Bayındır Bey.
Human beings make mistakes.
I am also a human being, Alçiçek.
Of course I might be wrong.
And I got it wrong many times.
But I didn't know the bond between
you and Aktemur was so strong.
If only I knew this...
I'd not promise Bayındır.
This is of no importance, Mother Sultan.
Our love was tested by your own fault.
We failed that test.
Both me and Aktemur.
It's over.
There is no need to talk about it.
It's not over, Alçiçek.
We both know very well.
I am the one who put
these birds in the cage.
I am the one who will free them.
I will bring you together.
And also...
Aktemur escaping from the dungeon...
Do you think I don't know it
was you who helped him?
Have you risked all this for
a love that's gone, Alçiçek?
Why do I ignore it?
Because you are like my daughter.
Be happy, be happy.
Your story that remained
incomplete because of me.
May it be completed.
This has become very
difficult, Mother Sultan.
I have the strength to do this.
You can go out now.
I shall command the preparations
for your wedding to begin.
Alçiçek and Aktemur.
You two need to get together.
You will be very happy.
You will think you are free.
You will always be at my command.
Can I come in?
Come in.
- Mother Sultan.
- Bengi Hatun.
- We have news from Esma.
- What is it?
We know where he is now.
Since we have overcome all calamities...
We will continue the
conquests from where we left off.
The death of Kantakuzenos...
will strike terror among them now.
They will be extra careful.
You should know the
latest news from Köprühisar.
It's time.
Cerkutay, you'll sneak
in with Ülgen Hatun.
Let me go too, my Bey, I know Köprüisar.
Tell Cerkutay what you know.
I need you, you'll be by my side.
Your command, my Bey.
Inshallah, we will know
everything in detail.
You should know the status of Köprühisar.
Then, Inshallah, we will
send our army there.
Inshallah.
My sons.
And you go to Sultan Mesut.
He would write letters
to Beys for rebellion.
His messages should be ready now.
You will take it and
distribute it to the Beys.
Take food to him and ask
him if he needs anything.
Your command, my Bey.
The situation is bad now, take a large
number of soldiers with you.
No.
The soldiers they have are enough.
They will manage on their own.
If the road is rough, so are
we, Mother Bala.
We'll manage.
Good.
Come on, my sons.
We know where Mesut is.
Take enough soldiers with you and go to the
place that Esma said about, and find Mesut.
Your command, my Sultan, come on!
We'll go to the Kayı tribe, come on.
My Bey, how long are we going to
keep Sultan Mesut with us?
Let those messages get answered first.
Let us know which Beys stand with us.
We will act accordingly.
We will, my Bey, but we are rebels.
İsmihan will not let us rest.
We have no business with rest, Boran.
Our path is always
fraught with difficulties.
Konur, you will establish headquarters
in Kızılca region.
But there'll be no siege weapons, you'll
only carry swords and do training.
Everything will be ready to
open when the time comes
Your command, my Bey.
As for İsmihan...
İsmihan...
She knows we are in the tribe.
She clearly had another plan.
Otherwise, she would have attacked us
with her army and tried to arrest us.
What is her plan, my Bey?
She will soon come and knock on our door.
We'll know when she comes.
- Can I come in, my Bey?
- Come in, Ayaz
Come.
My Bey, Mother Sultan is coming.
Let her come and see.
Let her come.
Sultan İsmihan is coming.
Are you ready, brother?
Always my brother, trust is more
important than our souls.
We've found traces, from this direction.
Come on, let's hurry.
Mesut must be here somewhere.
We won't stop until we find them.
The valiants of Osman Bey are
coming, Hadrat Sultan.
They also bring food.
Mashallah.
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
I hope you are well, Hadrat Sultan.
Thank Allah.
I brought food for you.
Hadrat Sultan Mesut.
Osman Bey said you would give
us some kind of trust. (an item)
True, letters will be sent to the
Beys, I have written them all.
My Bey!
My Bey, Mother Sultan's men are coming.
What are we going to do, brother?
I have a plan.
We'll get through them.
Listen to me carefully now.
Put down the swords.
Alps!
You also lower your swords.
I did not come here to arrest
you or to fight you.
So, tell me why you came here...
Mother Sultan.
Head of Kantakuzenos...
Is it a gift or a
threat, Osman Bey?
I came to ask
you about this.
Let it be what you want it to be.
If you are against me...
it's a threat.
But if you are not against me...
Then, it is my gift to you.
While we thought you escaped from court...
Our ally wanted
to execute you.
This makes him my enemy.
He has found
what he deserves.
And the enemy of my enemy is my friend.
For this reason, it was a
beautiful gift, Osman Bey.
But the nice thing...
is that you escaped from
his hands in some way.
This is a success worth appreciating.
Receiving appreciation
from you is our last wish.
Really, Osman Bey?
The fact that my appreciation
is a great gain...
and no matter how much
Bala Hatun refused our affection...
The only thing I want is
Allah's favor, Mother Sultan.
We never bring evil.
And what next, Osman Bey? Shall we
talk like this in front of the door?
If you don't tell us why you came...
You have no place inside, Mother Sultan.
All the mistakes I made
and the attempts of rebellion you made...
and your rebellious
words and rude behavior...
They were all overlooked by the
merciful Seljuk Sultan Alaeddin.
You are innocent now, Osman Bey.
Now there are some important
things we need to talk about.
Let's talk privately if possible.
Please, Mother Sultan.
There is no importance to others, let
us pursue the Sultan.
You can't escape anymore, Sultan Mesut.
I'll take you to Mother Sultan.
You should not be
deceived by what you see.
You are...
Do you think it is so easy, Avcı Bey?
They will come secretly.
First, we'll lure them into the woods and
then we'll shoot them with arrows.
Kumral Abdal! Change your
clothes with the Sultan.
Take this, Kumral Abdal.
My Bey.
Come on!
Change your clothes quickly.
Hurry up.
My brother! You will be next to
the warriors and Sultan Mesut.
Your command, my brother.
You little devil.
You are playing with me, right?
And you were fooled by this game, Avcı.
Don't be so eager to take
your soul, so go your way.
I will not go anywhere
without taking Sultan.
Let's go.
Orhan.
Maintaining trust is what we inherited
from our ancestors, Sultan Mesut.
Don't worry about my brother
and Kumral Abdal.
They just do what needs to be done.
And now we're going to take you to
a place to stay for a while.
You both possess the beautiful qualities
of Osman Bey, Inshallah.
Thank you, Sultan Mesut.
I give you back what you lost.
As you've read, Osman Bey, this is the
document with which I give you Yenişehir again.
Mother Sultan.
So, you're giving me Yenişehir again?
Alps!
Come here.
This is Hasan Alp.
The son of Abdurrahman Agha.
Abdurrahman Agha is one of
the merchants of Yenişehir.
He is a pottery dealer.
And he has four sons.
The eldest of them is Hğseyin.
He is Hasan's older brother.
He was among my Alps.
He fell a martyr in my arms.
The youngest daughter is Züleyha.
She was fighting the
disease in Yenişehir.
She got better, thank Allah.
And so on...
This is Kemal Alp.
The son of Fatma Mother.
Fatma Mother has five animals.
She sells milk in Yenişehir.
All her children and grandchildren
are Alps of Yenişehir.
Fatma Mother lost her husband as a martyr
in the conquest of Kulucahisar Castle.
She told me when the conquests stopped.
"Why do you stop, Osman Bey?"
"Why do you stop?"
"Did I lose my husband as a martyr so that
you would stop your conquests?"
Alps, you can come out now.
What I will say is...
You did not take Yenişehir from me.
So, you can't give it to me.
The only thing you'll take is
the property.
Not the hearts of my people.
The only thing you'll need
is a dry handful of soil.
Did we grow up
with what others gave us?
We take what we want
when we want it.
What we didn't lose... huh?
No.
No need for that.
You refuse what
Mother Sultan gives you.
This is not a rational
decision, Osman Bey.
As much as there are people whose
hearts are with you...
there are people whose
hearts aren't with you.
There are people among your followers
who are tired of being dragged...
into one adventure after another.
There are those who are tired of losing
their families as martyrs...
for the sake of your endless greed.
Of course, there are people like that.
And we will all end up in the dust, so
why all this trouble?
Let there be those who do
not understand the purpose of this.
There is no harm in not understanding
the purpose of this as well.
But he who understands the purpose of
our case will surely tell you.
Osman Bey, the Bey of the
rebellious border regions.
So, you don't accept what I offer you.
Will you continue your
calling with one tribe?
Your roots are not here.
You did not grow up
in this country.
How long will you be able to withstand in
these limits after this tyranny?
Until death.
Borders belong to us.
We will defend it together.
That is why I have given you
your city back.
You know better.
The issue is getting bigger...
Osman Bey.
Tomorrow, the Beys of Germiyanids,
the Beys of Karasids...
and the Beys of Isfendiyarids
will meet in court.
And you too will come.
I will answer the
invitation, Mother Sultan.
I swear I'm starting to get scared.
What is so secretive?
This is it, Ülgen.
Come on, put on this armor.
I'm wearing it?
Yes.
No... What...
How do I?
What?
Oh.
What's going on, girls?
First the sword and
now this shield!
Will I be the in The Sisters?
No, Ülgen...
You will do an important job.
Job?
What job is this?
A very important job.
Don't panic.
What can I do with
İsmihan with a sword and a shield?
İsmihan?
No, I can't do it.
She will devour me, she
will devour me raw.
I can't do it. Many
soldiers have already come.
No, Ülgen, it's not like that.
What?
Bengi Hatun.
She is burying me alive, girl.
Köprühisar, Ülgen.
You will sneak into
Köprühisar and collect information.
I thought you were going
to say something serious.
What?
Will I become a spy?
Alone?
In Köprühisar?
Oh, Ülgen...
It is written in your destiny to go to
the infidels alone on a mission.
Forgive me.
Ülgen, come on.
Stop it, Ülgen, stop it.
Is it possible that we throw
you into the flames alone?
You won't go alone
Osman Bey will give you a
distinguished road companion.
Who?
Cerkutay Alp will go with you.
Cerkutay?
He messes things up.
I'll go on my own.
Okay, then.
I'll tell Osman Bey...
He might agree.
Okay, no problem.
Osman Bey ordered that.
We cannot say more than he said.
Well then. Let him come.
He'll learn how to become a spy.
Come on, Ülgen, come on.
Come on, quickly put this on.
Well.
This is... the front end.
Is that so?
Ülgen.
It doesn't fit.
Not like that, Ülgen, not like that.
What's the matter, Mother Sultan?
You said it was very urgent.
I don't know how you came.
It's good, Bengi Hatun.
I will give you an important job.
Your command.
From now on...
The future of the Kayı
clan is in your hands.
And how will this happen? I am
not related to the Kayı tribe.
Yes...
but you will be.
You will let Aktemur and Alçiçek marry.
Mother Sultan.
This is not possible.
Ask me what you want.
Ask for my soul and
I'll give it to you.
But this can not...
I can not...--
I said my word...
Bengi Hatun.
Use your mind.
No matter how much we oppose it...
We will not be able to
prevent it from happening.
Mother Sultan.
This can not...-
If I make my daughter a
bride for the Kayıs...
I will lose her forever.
- This is...
- Bengi Hatun!
She asks for reconciliation and peace.
She also wanted to give you Yenişehir.
What can she seek
from that move, my Bey?
She got trapped.
What pushed her to peace...
is a problem that makes her need us.
It is definitely a big problem.
Maybe, my Bey.
Perhaps she understood that things
couldn't be done with Öktem and Bayındır...
so she wanted you by her side.
She has already invited Beys.
But...
She is still trying to get
close to us though.
Obviously there is something else.
But what we know now...
is that she needs us.
So, what do we do, my Bey?
Since she needs us...
We'll get what we want then.
And one of the things we want...
is Köprühisar.
The spy is ready, my Bey.
To not to lose your daughter...
You will accept this.
Aktemur and Alçiçek will marry.
Think for...
tomorrow.
When Osman came down
from his chair tomorrow...
I will declare Aktemur Bey.
And you will stand behind your son-in-law.
And you will rule the Kayı tribe.
Aktemur is not like his uncle Osman.
He is softer.
You can use him however you want.
How will this happen?
If I want it to happen, it will happen.
Also, that young man loves
your daughter very much.
And there is nothing easier than
controlling a young man in love...
Bengi Hatun.
Aktemur will become your son-in-law.
And you will rule the entire Kayı.
And when you rule Kayı...
I will rule the borders.
Söğüt
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam.
You have increased our honor.
Thank you.
You summoned me, my Sheikh.
Sit down, Osman Bey.
It's been a long time
we haven't met to chat.
Chatting with friends is important.
It increases sincerity.
I wanted to...
get closer.
Because...
Devil does not stand still.
When he finds a small crack...
it slips off
it immediately.
There is no crack (division)
between us, my Sheikh.
We will not allow the Devil
to get between us.
All our quarrels are over, Inshallah.
Isn't it, Osman Bey?
Of course, my Sheikh.
The tongue speaks...
and we hear.
But..
There is something that no one hears.
The language of hearts.
Is it saying the same thing?
Can Satan
really not touch this brotherhood?
I brought you word from
Commander Nayman, Mother Sultan.
Commander Nayman has learned about
Samagar's death.
So, he wants a big blood money...
and he will increase taxes.
Otherwise...
Your lands will be stained with blood.
How dare you, soldier!
You provoke my sword.
Know
whose presence you stand in!
I don't have anything to do with Samagar.
You have to make whoever knocked his
head off pay his blood money.
Not just Osman.
You will also pay the price.
You will all pay the price.
Samagar was in your protection.
Take him out.
If you don't listen to me now...
The only thing you will hear...
is the cries of your followers.
I will hear you...
but tomorrow.
Osman and the rest of the
Beys will also be here.
And you will say whatever
you want in front of them
Get out of my here now.
You will pay for this, you
will pay for this!
You will pay the price!
The ambassador will appear before me
tomorrow while the Beys are in the court.
Don't screw this up as
you couldn't catch Mesut.
What is the purpose of
this move, Mother Sultan?
It is certain that Osman will not
accept Nayman's requests.
All Beys will testify to his disobedience.
Osman will remain alone in this war.
You must be more knowledgeable
than me, Mother Sultan, but...
You say Mongols...
Do you think they will simply leave here after
everything's over and Osman is defeated?
All of them will
struggle with this problem.
And with each move, their
need for me will increase.
As always, you made the right choice.
Not so much, Bayındır Bey.
I will have those Kayıs step by step.
I will make Aktemur and Alçiçek marry...
and make Aktemur the
head of the Kayı tribe.
Tell me, Turgut Bey.
Öktem Bey is currently
supporting İsmihan.
Doesn't that ever bother you?
My Sheikh...
And what about you, Osman Bey?
When İsmihan's enmity became clear...
Didn't it occur to you to say, "Turgut Bey, see
with whom you have cooperated"?
"Turns out I was right."
Whoever says "I" is wrong.
Traitors will always be alone.
You can't be a friend until
your first word is "you".
He who does not put his friend
above himself cannot be a true friend.
There are many examples of
friendship among the Companions.
But there is a specific incident.
Even the infidels were amazed.
What is it, my Sheikh?
After the Hudaybiyah defeat...
The infidels were so angry...
and they did all forms of treachery.
Zeyd and Hubeyb...
fell into the hands of the infidels.
And they took them to Mecca.
And there, they sold them to the infidels.
And when they took Zeyd to the side of
the Kaaba to kill him treacherously...
Abu Sufyan approached
him and asked him.
He told him, "Tell the truth."
In return for making you
reunite with your family safely...
"Wouldn't you have wanted Muhammad to be in your place and to be killed in your place now?"
Zeyd turned to him and said, "Never."
I don't even want him to get hurt...
while I was sitting with
my family, let alone this.
The infidels were very surprised by Zeyd's
attachment to the Messenger of Allah.
And the Quraish leader admitted that...
saying...
“I have not seen anyone love someone as
the companions of Muhammad love Muhammad.”
To care about your friend more than
yourself...
We learn that from Muhammad
and the Companions.
It is a heartbreak that
destroys the infidels.
This is why friends should let nothing
come between them, not even themselves.
So that Satan does not find an
opportunity to get between them.
And only when this happens, we do
not give a chance to the infidels.
It is enough to remember this.
Alright, my Sheikh.
Well.
Do you allow us to enter?
Princes.
Go ahead.
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam.
My sons.
Apparently, the job was done properly.
Thank Allah, my Bey.
Mashallah.
İsmihan.
She sentAvcı after us.
But we beat them, my Bey.
What about Sultan Mesut?
He is in good hands.
He is with Kumral Abdal.
As you said, father, they constantly change
their place and leave no trace behind.
On the one hand, İsmihan behaves
as if she is approaching us.
On the one hand, she makes Avcı
follow Sultan Mesut.
She doesn't stop, as if what she
did to me wasn't enough.
She keeps playing.
Let her play whatever she wants.
We are the ones who will
make the real game.
Thank you, sons.
May Allah bless the brave.
Mashallah.
Hatun!
Do you hear what
you say?
Is this logical to you?
Öktem Bey.
My daughter once came back
through the door of that palace.
I'll never allow
something like this again.
Don't you hear me?
Mother Sultan is right.
As we can't stand up to them, then
we'll take advantage of this matter.
I thought Aktemur
was a good man...
until he let my daughter down.
I no longer trust that young man.
We'll forget what Aktemur did.
Aktemur is a fine young
man, quiet and respectful.
As his father, Gündüz Bey.
What I mean is, if you make him love you
and respect you, he won't go against your word.
He's not as greedy as Bayındır.
It's true what you're saying, it's true.
Aktemur is young.
He's easily controlled.
If the Mother Sultan does what she said
and put Aktemur on the throne...
We will become the strongest
tribe in the borders.
Our daughter does
not become our enemy.
And she
marries the one she loves.
And we are getting stronger.
Yes.
But, Bengi Hatun...
I will not repeat that mistake.
Know that.
Alçiçek.
Come here, my daughter.
Come.
Yes, father.
Now, my daughter...
I will ask you a question.
But you will tell me the truth.
Okay?
Do you still want to marry Aktemur?
Tell me.
Yes.
I will go tomorrow and talk to Ayşe Hatun.
And we will solve
this matter.
Good.
Hadrat Mother Sultan.
Beys' units entered Söğüt.
Beys will come soon.
Good.
Let them come.
Hadrat Mother Sultan.
If you'll excuse me, I'd
like to ask you a question.
Did you summon the Beys just to
unite against the Mongols?
Because I know you like to kill
two birds with one stone.
You understand, Bayındır.
Sometimes, you understand everything.
Osman will not consider my words.
He accuses me of arrogance.
He sees that my words are meaningless.
But the Beys' ability would give
him conclusive evidence.
You'll show him that the state isn't left
for him and will make him feel small.
It'll be like a slap, Bayındır.
On the one hand, we will unite, and on
the one hand, we will crush Osman.
You thought well, Mother Sultan.
You thought well.
Osman needs to face this fact.
If you'll excuse me...
I don't want to
participate in the court.
What's the reason?
Mother Sultan, as you know, a poor man
like me has no place in that court.
The elephants will battle, let the little
weeds do their thing outside.
As you like...
Bayındır Bey.
Bayındır won't sit still, he knows
what he's going to do.
I have always opposed this, Ayşe Hatun.
But...
They said "Don't speak
words bigger than you."
So?
I made a mistake.
But I got my mistake.
You can't stand in front of love
even if you are a stone wall.
Do you know how many people's hearts you
broke until you understood your mistake?
I know for sure.
I know, that's why I came.
I want to make up for my mistake.
And you should understand me.
I did not suffer pain that
could be easily forgotten.
What I want to say is...
If your son still loves my daughter...
Come and ask for her.
It's up to you now.
The court that İsmihan will hold is different
from the Beys' council that we hold.
We are not her companions, but
we will be her guests.
Know that this place will be
different from the field of war.
But what you should know...
it that it will be a war of words, not
a war of the wrist.
So, all of you will control your anger.
Yakup Bey, from Germiyanids, whose borders
extend from the east to the far west...
and the owner
of the largest armies...
will be there.
Qarasi Bey, whose line extends
back to Danishmend Ghazi...
and who is the
ruler of the seas in the West...
will be there too.
Şemseddin Yaman Jandar Bey, of the
Jandar tribe, the ruler of Eflani...
who wants to include
Kütahya to his lands...
will also be there.
Everyone will talk.
Even if they say something worth
cutting their tongue, my Bey...
Shall we shut up?
You will be silent, Boran.
The smallest of them is
five times as many as us.
With their warriors and their possessions.
At the slightest mistake, we'll be like the
one who goes to the fire with the blower.
Thank you, my Bey, as you command.
They are bigger than us and they
outnumber us.
They are stronger than us.
However, Inshallah...
We equalize them in strength.
Eyvallah, my Bey!
If Allah allows, we will take what
we want and get out of there!
- God willing, sir - God willing
Come on, apls.
Let's go.
Let's go
Are you scared, Ulgen Hatun!?
Hatun-tun!
Tun.
Why would I be scared?
I am the daughter of the black angel.
Oh.
I fear the fear.
Just care yourself.
Me?
I was born to fear, to fear!
Yes, you were. You are never scared(!)
Hatun! Allah Allah!
Of course I'm never scared.
When did you see me scared?
Well, I'm not going to lie.
I never saw you scared.
But I know it!
You're a coward, Cerkutay Alp.
You are not afraid of the enemy.
However...
You are scared of the person
riding next to you right now.
It's true.
Who is not scared of their heart!
Wait for me!
Wait!
Why did Bengi Hatun come?
Does she know we got Alcicek
out of the dungeon?
It's none of your business why she came.
Didn't you give up on Alcicek?
Indeed.
Yes, but...
If she learned that,
she will disturb her.
Of course she will.
What's more, she might have even locked
the girl inside a room.
She learned, right?
What shall we do?
How will we save Alcicek?
Aktemur!
You still love this girl!
And you regret that you rejected her,
don't you?
It doesn't matter now, mother.
Tell me!
Do you regret or not?
That day...
I was at the face of death
I closed my eyes and turned to the Creator.
But at that exact moment...
I had a thought.
I left Alcicek behind, whom I misjudged.
I broke her heart.
I regret.
Okay then.
Go make it up to her.
We'll ask her for marriage this evening.
Sogut
Welcome Osman Bey!
Come on!
Osman Bey, you will enter the court of
the great Beys of the Attic Seljuk state.
We have known you for a long time
Please hand over your swords.
Son.
You just told me you've known me
for a long time.
Then you should also known that
I always carry my sword with me.
Yet you still try to be nice.
Thank you.
Cut this nonsense, Osman Bey!
When the state orders you to hand them over,
you hand them over!
You see my sword is in its scabbard.
If you ever see it out of the scabbard...
It will be the last thing you see.
You tried to take it from me.
You can't do it unless you die.
Soldiers!
Alps!
Hand over your swords,
no blood will be spilled today
Put down your swords.
Baysungur!
My Bey.
Peace be upon you.
And may peace be upon you too.
Attention, Hadrat Mother Sultan!
Where are the Beys, Mother Sultan?
They are coming from a long way.
They are coming with a big convoy.
I appreciate them.
They are kind to come, Osman Bey.
Welcome.
Welcome my Bey.
Welcome!
The Bey of Candarogullari
Semseddin Yaman Candar Bey
Welcome, my Bey!
The Bey of Karesiogullari
Kalemsahoglu Karesi Bey
Welcome, my Bey!
Welcome, Karasi Bey.
The Bey of Germiyanogullari
Yakup Bey
Welcome my Bey!
Allah bless you my Bey!
The Bey of Candarogullari
The owner of far lands
The ruler of the rural areas...
Semseddin Yaman Candar Bey.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
Welcome, Candar Bey.
I brought many presents, Mother Sultan.
Here are our crops that we trade from north to south
and from land to sea in the four corners of the world
All of them are the best.
Perhaps even your palace hasn't tasted
this quality.
Thank you.
The nightmare of Byzantine.
Who extended his control
from Edremit to Bandirma
The killer of the infidels, Karasi Bey!
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
Welcome, Karasi Bey.
Thank you, Mother Sultan.
We have come in response to your invitation.
This is the sword my father Kalem Shah
slayed the infidels with, in the conquest of Biga.
My daughter's husband, Uslu Bey.
He is as valuable as
the sword we gifted.
Thank you, Karasi Bey.
Governor of the region from Angro to Kutahya
The owner of the strongest
tribes and the strongest armies
The protector of the Germiyanogullari,
Yakup Bey.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
What is this?
Are you greeting us with your sword
in your hands, Mother Sultan?
Welcome, Yakup Bey.
We heard your name, Osman Bey.
Finally here we are meeting.
Everything is waiting for its time,
Yakup Bey.
No, not for its time.
Everything is waiting for you to
stand still.
We hear you in Constantinople.
Then we hear you are in Konya.
He who wanders a lot gets
himself into many misfortunes
We are the sons of a traveling generation.
Standing still is not for us.
We love to visit the trouble.
So that it doesn't come to our land.
I love nomads very much.
I always give them lands.
But if you are a nomad,
you should know your place.
And you have to learn to leave that dream
to those who deserve to dream it,
to those whose lineage extends back to the state
Everyone brought their gifts, Yakup Bey.
Did you bring nothing?
My gift is not small enough to be carried.
Your gift is outside Sogut.
Three hundred horses,
each one more powerful than the other
Thank you, Yakup Bey.
Go ahead.
Osman Bey.
Please.
Why are our Beys not sitting, Mother Sultan?
They stand in the place
they deserve, Osman Bey.
You should be thankful to Mother Sultan
as she lets you sit with such Beys.
We are not that kind of people who are grateful to
a human being as they have given us credit, Candar Bey.
We get our possessions and our lands
with our own power.
Don't confuse us with you.
Beys.
Sit behind me.
Please, of course.
They must be weakened after all
the long way.
We can hear Mother Sultan now.
The situation is worse than you think.
There's news from Commander Nayman.
The beheading of his commander, Samagar,
angered him greatly.
He asks us to give more taxes.
And to pay blood money for the head of Samagar.
Mother Sultan!
We are here to listen to you about
the part that concerns us.
The one who caused this shall
pay the price himself alone.
Who killed Samagar?
Karasi Bey.
Suppose I killed him
Do not look at Osman Bey like that.
Since when killing the enemy
has been a bad thing?
I called you for unity.
Mother Sultan.
Where do you get your strength from?
What kind of question is that, Yakup Bey?
You get it from your son, the ruler of the
Attic Seljuk Empire, Sultan Alaeddin
Will we unite with this Bey who wanted to
dethrone our Sultan and tried to kidnap Masut?
Forget about us.
How did you forgive him?
Only the helpless hold a grudge.
Only the weak get angry.
While the strong forgive.
His Holiness Sultan Alaeddin forgave Osman Bey.
If we accept this and want unity
You also should do the same, Yakup Bey.
The war with the infidels exhausted my armies.
But wars bring trophies.
I suggest paying the taxes and accepting
thedemanded blood money.
And I am doing this only for you,
Mother Sultan.
Otherwise nor Osman Bey...
Nor these lands are worthy of
any tax or gold.
If gold holds the Turks' land...
Let it be burned down!
The freedom that is bought with money
is lost when the money is gone.
If we owe our lives to gold,
let it be redeemed.
Osman Bey.
Calm down a bit.
Nobody has the intention of
losing their freedom.
If we need to give blood money, we will.
If we need to fight, we fight.
We are here for unity and to
search for a solution
The solution to this is not blood money,
Mother Sultan.
I took these areas with my own blood.
And I built it with my blood
Not blood money, but I won't even give
my dog for Samagar's head.
You heard me.
Emperor's Palace
Constantinie.
Emperor Andranikos.
The ring of Kantakouzanos
whom you serve came faster than you, Olof.
I am only in the service
of Holy Jesus, Emperor.
If our path unites, I'll be in your service too.
Kantakouzanos got the end he deserved, Olof.
If I didn't believe you...
...I would bury you next to him.
And now I will resurrect
the things he demolished
The cross on your neck.
I had heard that you became a Christian.
But this was hard to believe.
What you heard is correct, Emperor.
I have chosen the religion of Holy Jesus.
I am shedding blood for one goal only.
And I will continue to spill it until
we expel all Muslims from our lands
Marcus.
I know that.
That is why I summoned you.
With what power, Osman Bey?
How will you fight?
Who got in our way like mountains...
...were crushed by us before.
Let them come.
If they come, they will go as they came.
Osman Bey!
While your hundred tent tribe
was looking for land to settle
We were crushing the Mongols.
You don't even have a history!
And who is the oldest Ghazi in your family?
Your dreams will fall into the water.
And you will be drowned in that water.
With what force will you fight?
With the same force with which
I bound Geyhatu and drove him from my land
I buried the enemies...
...enemies that you are afraid to mention.
When I was fighting the
Mongols and the Byzantines...
None of you were here.
So don't make any decisions on my land.
You wouldn't even be able to if
you didn't know Mother Sultan.
Otherwise...
You will be crushed.
- Osman Bey!
- Enough!
This is all of our issue.
Hide your anger for the enemy.
We shall, Mother Sultan, we shall.
However...
Instead of making
an effort to achieve an agreement...
...Osman Bey is trying to fight us!
Candar Bey.
Protecting homeland is a war.
But if you want us to convince you...
You have to ask yourself sincerely first.
Otherwise, we'll start thinking you do not
care about the cause.
You must be Turgut Bey.
You are the shadow of Osman Bey.
We are the shadow of good,
but I see you have become evil itself.
Dear Mother Sultan, I beg your pardon
We didn't come here to hear insults.
It's a difficult issue, but...
I don't trust these Beys.
- Excuse me
- Candar Bey!
Unless I say the meeting is over...
No one dares to take a single step!
I'm waiting for you to be seated.
The messenger is waiting for a decision from us.
If we are going to fight,
then the decision to go to war
And if we are going to
increase taxes and pay blood money
We will send this decision.
And now...
The messenger of the Mongols has come,
Mother Sultan.
Let him.
Commander Naiman wants you to pay
blood money for Samagar.
And he commands to raise taxes to three times more
because of your disobedience.
And he wants Osman's head, too.
Olof, I have gathered
a huge army against the Muslims
You are the one who will lead this army.
You are going to serve the cross you wear
on your neck, even if it is at the cost of your life.
I will continue to serve Holy Jesus
until my last breath
With this army...
I will spill rivers of blood of those
who want to extinguish the light of Holy Jesus.
And this will not be very difficult.
Ismihan shattered their unity
And now they are uniting
to face the threat of the Mongols
And you will stand with Ismihan.
You run your job secretly.
Until they realise the army of Holy Jesus
in their lands.
Then our unity will end them.
We will no longer wait for our
enemies behind walls.
We will kill them in the fields.
Listen to me well now, Olof.
I could not hear.
Say it again.
I knew the Beys were fools,
but now I know they are also deaf.
Naiman wants blood money for Samagar
and taxes for your disobedience
In addition to your helpless head.
If I give him my head,
will he leave my country alone?
No, he'll keep taking
the taxes and blood money.
If you object, he will turn your lands into hell
We will take your head anyway, Osman.
He wants my head, did I hear right?
Now that he wants my head.
I will give you neither my head.
Nor the taxes that you want unjustly.
The only thing I will give you.
is death.
And now...
Take this to Commander Neiman.
If he wants to end up like this...
Tell him that Osman Bey
is waiting for him in his homeland.
Go.
Osman Bey, what have you done?
I have made my opinion clear.
We will fight.
Did you ask us?
Will you involve me in the war
without asking me?
Don't trust your abundant gold.
And do not brag that you have many alps.
You are many, but we are equal to you.
If you have a brave heart,
you will fight with us.
But if you are not brave..
We are brave, and we have alps.
But you want to push us to
a war in which we will be erased!
Neyman's armies are huge.
Those who were warned,
“Your enemies have mobilized their
q forces against you, so fear them,”
the warning only made them grow stronger in faith...
and they replied, “Allah ˹alone˺ is sufficient ˹as an aid˺
for us and ˹He˺ is the best Protector.”
[Surah Ali Imran - 173]
Right now...
I await your decisions.
We will all see together if you
are true warriors and believers.
Do you think she'll come?
No?
I offended her greatly.
She won't come.
Alcicek.
Look.
Do you see?
I said she would come.
Are you telling me I am a fool?
You're right.
If it had been the old Alcicek,
she would not have come.
But this is the new Alcicek.
She is stupid.
She hears the sound of her heart.
She can't stop herself.
No.
She is talking about me.
I'm the fool.
I didn't listen to my heart.
I am the one who hurt his lover.
I'm the one who left her
in the middle of the road.
Though...
I have come to my senses now.
Tell me.
Is it too late to regret?
Can you forgive this man who did not allow
the tears to dry in those beautiful eyes?
How do I trust the man who
left me in the middle of the road?
What if he does the same thing again?
No.
I will not.
I can't.
Trust me.
How can I trust your words?
I swear on this tree, birds and the soil...
I swear on my beloved.
That I will never leave you again,
Alcicek.
Tell me.
Can you forgive me?
I forgive you.
But this was your last chance.
Last chance.
Sogut.
Osman.
I knew he would declare war.
But what he did...
When Neiman comes, Osman will regret
refusing my help.
Osman Bey thinks that the Beys will follow him
after this show of his!
He thinks that Beys respect him
and that he has satisfied them.
You will write a letter to each Bey, Avci.
You will send them,
and no one will ally with Osman.
As you order, my Sultan.
Osman Bey.
In this way he went out
to establish a state...
...he'll be history.
I know we have a lot of problems, my Bey.
Ismihan on one side.
- The Mongols on the other side,but...
- We certainly have a lot of problems.
We want to do a good job, my Bey.
I know very well what you're going to say.
Do you think Aktemur agrees?
Actimor agrees, my Bey.
If you would agree too...
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come on, Aktemur.
Germiyan and Karesi tribes
ceased trading with us.
And Cobanogullari put a limit on the trade.
We don't have relationships only with them,
so we'll overcome their absence.
Aktemur.
Come here.
Let's talk, man to man.
The caravanserai near Kobrohisar
Whatever!
This is so boring!
I was going to be a spy!
It was a mistake to partner up with you.
I told Bala Hatun that
I needed to do this on my own.
That Cerkutay would encumber me!
Yes, if you weren't be with me,
who would you be with?
Everyone but you.
But they insisted a lot and said Jerkotay
must come.
I found it.
- What did you find?
- I found it, I found it.
I swear I found it
Tell me what did you find, man?
I found what I was looking for.
Tell me, Aktemur.
Are you sure of your love this time?
Know that I won't forgive you one more time.
Uncle.
I was always sure of my love.
But my anger blinded my eyes.
I broke Alcicek's heart.
I made a mistake.
Son.
You will fight for your love.
You will follow her.
You shouldn't collapse in a tiny damage.
Love does not forgive mistakes.
There will be no mistake anymore uncle.
From now on it's time to heal
the heart I've broken
I spoke with Alcicek,
made it up for her.
Eyvallah.
Then I'll do what I need to do.
But there is something else.
Oktem Bey.
He is with Ismihan.
We will become relatives in this marriage.
Uncle, if you don't want to...
No, don't worry, I'll do what I have to do.
The smell of blood coming from Ingol...
...will cause a burning sensation
in the farthest part of Osman's nose
We will avenge everything we have lost so far,
not just what we lost in Ingöl
Finally, my love.
It will make amends for us, my love
We are now stronger than ever.
Here comes our only friend among them.
Come, Bayindir, come, my old friend.
This is a sign of our friendship.
We are enemies in front of the eyes
and friends in the absence of eyes.
I will give you whatever you ask for Inegol.
Inegol.
But that will remain between the two of us.
I see, Bayindir, I see.
Considering you even share your gold,
what you say must be true.
So, Ismihan lost your friendship, too.
Yes.
Let them think Bayindir is a fool.
I will kill them all with you.
We'll both be good partners, Olof.
We will be good partners.
We were already good, Bayindir.
We were good until Ismihan.
Then she possessed both of us.
Alcicek.
Osman will go to ask Alcicek for marriage.
Is this Alcicek the girl you couldn't marry?
Stop there, Hatun.
The bride has not yet mounted the horse.
Only Allah knows what will happen in the end
Who will attend the ceremony?
Everyone will be there from Ismihan to Turgut.
They will certainly take measures, however...
The headless herd quickly disperses.
Well, take advantage of this opportunity, Olof.
I will take Inegol.
This doesn't fit me!
I look terrible!
You are such a joke, Cerkutay!
It suits you, you look very beautiful.
Come on, walk, walk, you're too slow.
Hurry up, come on.
A beautiful word does not come
out of your mouth!
I'm tired of walking!
Why did we leave those horses
behind and go on foot?
Let's go.
That jaw only works for eating.
Hey, I ask you where we are going!
What are you looking at?
Are you seeing my face for the first time?
It is not going to work like that.
You look very beautiful and very clean.
Close your eyes, close, close.
You are out of your mind!
What are you doing, you crazy!?
You're absolutely insane.
You had a brain that big, and it's gone too!
Come on, come on, here, here!
Stop! Stop!
What do you want?
Stop!
They raided our inn.
My sister and I, we...
Sister!
We could hardly run away with our lives.
Yes, yes, I am his sister!
Forever sister!
Help us, help us!
Take us with you at least to Kupruhisar.
Mongols want to finish the job.
For that reason we will not leave our tribes
and all our possessions without measures.
We will always be ready.
Mongols will attack us soon as you killed
their messenger.
So what about the wedding, Osman Bey?
Oktem cannot make any move
without their knowledge.
Obviously, the wedding is part of the game.
Once we know the game...
We will be victorious.
My Bey.
If they set up a game, taking advantage
of my love, I'll kill them all.
We'll settle the accounts.
Don't worry.
Are the preparations done?
We are always ready, my Bey.
We don't take any breath
without our swords, my Bey.
Let's go and take Alcicek.
And if they play a game,
we will take their lives then.
Praise be.
The alps and sisters
who will bring gifts are also armed, my Bey.
Don't worry.
Praise be upon you, Hatuns.
Come on then alps, hatuns!
- Come on!
- Come on, come on!
Welcome, Mother Sultan.
Thank you Oktem Bey.
Brothers!
We have taken all our might
into the enemy's homeland!
Now is the time for us to cling
tightly to our own country
We will make Inegol our home!
Our brothers died.
If we die, we die for our land!
But first we will kill everyone in Inegol!
And we will give it as a gift
to our brothers who will come from the north!
We will give them a homeland,
and we will also give them the light of Jesus!
- Are you with me, my brothers?
- We're with you, Olof
Let Jesus enlighten our way
Come on, come on, Dan
- Did you start the fires?
- Yes.
I have set fires in all the villages around Inegol,
as you have requested
Lovely.
Soon the Ingol alps
will go out to put out these fires.
We'll run in when the door opens.
- Are you with me, my brothers?
- We're with you, Olof
My Alcicek.
You finally managed it, huh?
I didn't do anything mother,
it's thanks to you.
But I didn't understand,
how did you change your mind?
Are you satisfied with my marriage?
My mind is not satisfied.
But if you ask me about my heart,
it is satisfied, my daughter.
If you are wondering when I changed my mind...
It changed that day you put the dagger
on your neck, Alcicek.
Since that day I have not rested
my head on the pillow peacefully.
I can't breathe since that day.
Mother.
My daughter.
My Cicek (flower in Turkish)
I still can't believe it.
It's like I'm in a dream.
You are not in a dream, my daughter.
May Allah open your path and luck for you, my daughter
Come on, go now and help with the preparations.
Come on.
Osman Bey must be soon to come.
I am satisfied just for now, duaghter.
Just for now.
- Boran
- My Bey!
Let the alps be well positioned in the outskirts
We don't know what Ismihan can do, be careful.
Yes my Bey.
- Peace be upon you.
- And peace be upon you too.
We have finally met together
for a good deed, Osman Bey.
Both good deeds and bad deeds
come from Allah, Mother Sultan.
This is the first time you come to Marmaracik
not chained up after the trial and the Kantakouzanos matter.
This is nice too.
It is true.
But when I came to Marmaragic,
my sword was in my hand
And it was covered in blood
This Marmaracik was given to
Oktem Bey by me.
If you want me to come like I did previously,
I can.
No, that's fine.
It is known that we no longer raise our swords against
each other, but rather against the enemy
Let this good deed be a sign of this.
Let us take the girl first,
let us perform our wedding.
And then we'll talk about
who will raise his sword against whom.
But I did not say that I would unite with you.
That will happen too, Osman Bey.
You are mature enough to forget bad
experiences for the sake of your future.
Let us finish this first.
Let's sit.
Ingol Castle
Hurry up, alps we need to
put out the fires before they get worse!
Stop! Open the gates.
Who are you? And what do you want?
Protect yourselves with shields!
Open!
Olof, shields are burning.
Close!
Attack!
By Allah's command and on
the Sunnah of the Messenger of God
I ask the hand of our daughter Alcicek
for my nephew Aktimur, who is like a son to me.
But I would first like to hear
Alcicek's response.
Let Mother Sultan and her father talk later.
Tell us, Alcicek, do you love Aktemur?
I love him, my Bey.
Oktem Bey.
We know our son Aktemur.
We know Aktemur Bey.
And we know his courage.
So he is worthy of our daughter.
And I, as her father, give her to him.
Congratulations.
Let this open a good path.
Allah bless you.
May Allah give you children and honor.
Amen.
But there are things that
will not happen again.
If my daughter comes to my door crying...
Then I will make you pay for this.
If anyone is hurt again..
I will kill them myself.
Eyvallah, Osman Bey.
Rest assured.
For the good of all to happen.
Thank Allah.
We witnessed these two young people's
togetherness finally.
This won't fail us, right Bayindir Bey?
I'm afraid.
What if Ismihan Sultan hears?
Huseyin Efendi.
Do I take you with me to be afraid?
Do not be afraid.
No one will ever know we're
secretly working with Olof.
Until we get the strength.
Look, look, do you hear this, Huseyin?
There's nothing this can't solve.
They can even open the gates of Inegol.
Did you facilitate Olof's work?
We did, Bayindir Bey.
Inegol belongs to Olof now.
Good.
You've been waiting for your job
without doing any work this whole time
And now you came in handy.
You will be handy again.
This is the reward for your work.
Don't hesitate, come on.
Inegol will be your grave, Olof.
You won't even have a grave.
I will not stop until I kill you all.
Inegol is the beginning.
But you won't see that.
They won't even find your dead bodies.
Inegol belongs to us now, Olof!
This place is our first land!
We will attack the Muslims from here!
We will light the light of Jesus Christ
from Inegol!
Remove the flags!
Congrats.
Congratulations, son.
Congratulations
Mother Sultan, Osman Bey.
We lost Inegol.
Did we lose Inegol?
How?
Who?
Olof, Olof, my Bey.
Olof?
What are you saying?
Turgut Bey!
He is just a messenger.
But I will eliminate Olof and the emperor
from whom he received the order!
Mongols weakened us.
But not to this degree!
If necessary, I will fight my last war
under the walls of Constantinople!
But I will never let infidels
take over the land of Turks!
If you have anything to do with this
Find yourself a place to hide.
What are you saying Osman Bey?
If I were to conquer Inegol,
would I ask your permission?
Do you think I can't take it
with one order of mine?
I took these lands with my own blood.
If I lose them with a game
you're involved in...
Then I will water this land
with your blood.
Visit our website for more: turkision.com